SUCHET MAHAJAN

Address: 542 L block Mahipalpur, New Delhi 110037 Email: suchet.mahajan5@hotmail.com | Telephone: 7053055561

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A young and well groom-boy with the highly motivated, person who is passionate about sale and marketing. I am the man who believes in customer satisfaction which leads the result to employee recognition and promotion. I have experience of 4.6 years with the skill of Microsoft Excel, Customer service, Telemarketing, B2B and B2C selling, Promotion plans such as ATL and BTL. Strong consulting professional with a Master of Business Administration (MBA) focused on sale and retail marketing from Chitkara University.

Area of Expertise

- Business Development
- Relationship management
- Lead Generation

- Sale presentation/demo
- Client Retention
- P&L Management

- Conflict management and resolution
- Revenue Generation
- Sale strategies

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- **Urban Ladder:** Achieved area of sale target 2.35 crore yearly
- Urban Ladder: Won Certificate of excellence beginner level
- Reliance Brand Ltd.: Setup of 3 stores at Indira Gandi Airport New Delhi
- Reliance Brand Ltd: Achieve ACE performance certificate from DIAL and GMR
- MBS Technologies: Successfully on-board 35 retailers and merchandiser across Himachal Pradesh

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Byjus|Business Development Trainee

Nov 2019-Feb 2020

ROLE AND RESPONSIBILITY

- Generating revenue by counselling prospects and converting them to sales
- Converting free app user to paid user through email, calling and Direct sale
- Handle B2C consoling and B2B consoling in school and colleges
- Take and process the order in an accurate manner
- Coordination with respective team for product service

URBAN LADDER | sale Associate

May 2018 – November 2019

ROLE AND RESPONSIBILITY

- Prioritize account management, POS operations, customer service problem-solving and relationship building in a fast-paced setting
- Generate Lead for all clients, prepare planogram, share catalogue by providing consultative input and convert leads into prospective sale
- Coordination with entire Urban Ladder internal team for best-suited solution for customer Answer all queries regarding delivery timing & location, product information, returns and exchanges etc. on phone and Email
- Execute all tasks such as Visual Merchandising, maintain store inventory by coordinating with the Operations and Sourcing team, Maintain store shrinkage less than 1%
- Execute a sale promotion scheme, analysis data and prepare an entry-level report, forecast sale

Reliance Brand Ltd | Sale Associate

January 2017 - May 2018

ROLE AND RESPONSIBILITY

- Work in sales team managed cash register, communicated with customers and operated sales floor. Exceeded sales and promotional goals consistently
- Enriching customer experience through high standard customer service product Knowledge
- Generate monthly individual revenue of 10-15 lakh and provided a daily sale report to store and territory manager
- Setup of 3 Hamley's store at Indira Gandhi International airport

MBS Technologies PVT. Ltd. |Team Leader sale and marketing-Field

May 2014- October 2015

- Selling all electronics such as CCTV cameras, biometrics, accounting software
- Find new market, Contracting and pricing negotiation with retailers and merchandisers stores
- Providing feedback to management in all selling products and feedback on what customers want and their needs
- Travelling and visiting the retailer, dealer and customer in Himachal Pradesh
- Cold calling, designing and circulation of pamphlets and analysis of an advertisement

EDUCATION

MBA(Sale and Retail Marketing)

Chitkara University, Chandigarh 2016-2018 with score 8.40 CGP Key Modules:

Business Skills; Operations Management; Economics, Business and Sustainability; Financial Accounting; Marketing Principles; Organisational Behaviour and Analysis; Business Ethics; Business Decision-Making

Other courses

- **Digital sale certificate** from Google Credential ID 36685462
- **The Fundamental of digital Marketing** *from Google* -Credential ID 7VT5N977P. Sales Approach and Coaching through Digitalization,
- Advance Google Analytics from Google. Data collection, analysis of data with an advance tool, advance marketing tool

SOFTWARES

Microsoft Office (PowerPoint, Word, Excel), CRM, ERP, SAP retail Microsoft Nav, Analytics tool such as Sisence, Google analytics